Lemonade is a music, tv movie film directed by Beyoncé.
The second "visual album" (a collection of short films) by Beyoncé, this time around she takes a piercing
look at racial issues and feminist concepts through a sexualized, satirical, and solemn tone.
Self, played by Beyoncé.
Self, played by Brittani Alexander.
Self, played by Jasmine Badie.
Self, played by Fulani Bahati.
Self, played by Chloe Bailey.
Self, played by Halle Bailey.
Lemonade is a 2016 musical film and visual album by American singer Beyoncé, and
serves as a visual companion to her 2016 album of the same name.
Beyoncé also contributes as a director and executive producer for the film.
The film was released on April 23, 2016, premiering on HBO, and bundled with the album,
which was released on the same day, on CD/DVD, Tidal and iTunes Store.
The film explores themes of southern usa, poetry,
empowerment, pop culture, music video.